In 1999, Ruden entered the Vietnamese market,
bringing with it over 150 years of experience in protecting the finances and
health of millions of families
worldwide.  With a
customer-centric philosophy,
Rudenal consistently strives for practical innovation
for its customers.  A prime example is innovating the
customer experience.  Rudencial collaborated with
experts and VN Express to
produce a series of articles on insurance: Understand it well,
buy the right one.  This helps customers understand
their rights and implements
call recording for consultations to ensure customers purchase
according to their needs and financial capabilities. It
also aims to expand the customer experience center model,
providing
fast and comprehensive service from consultation to
contract management and claims processing.
We also deployed
model general agency offices to meet the
ever-changing needs of our
customers and launched the Ring Green Future unit-linked fund
.  The first unit-linked fund
in the Vietnamese life insurance market
offers customers who own
unit-linked insurance products the
option to invest in a
sustainable way, benefiting
them both today and in the future.  When
customers need help the most, the
insurance claim processing is
very quick, helping
customers and their families overcome difficulties.
In the first half of 2025, Rudeno
made payments totaling VND 7,410 billion, accounting for over 25% of the
entire industry.
Brudent's customer-centric efforts have been recognized with
prestigious awards.
We also continuously improve the
quality of our consultants.  Regular
intensive training sessions are organized
to help consultants improve their
expertise in selling effectively and comprehensively, and to build
long-term relationships with clients.  Rudal also
collaborates with the FSB Institute at FBT University to
implement a
business management training program for
general agency office managers and
focuses on developing
MDRT consultants, a globally recognized designation
for leading professionals
in the life insurance and
financial services fields with
outstanding expertise and skills, always putting the
client's best interests first.  Thanks to this,
we achieved the number 1 position in the
Vietnamese market and 12th globally in terms of the
number of MDRT members.
Ruden also innovated its strategy for
sustainable community development.
Smart finance project.   The
Safe School Project was created to
improve financial literacy and traffic safety knowledge
for Vietnamese children.  The "
Giving Love to Black Vietnam" program
contributed 1 billion VND through the Vietnam Children's Protection Fund
to support
flood relief efforts.  We also work alongside the
Vietnamese government to achieve its goal of
building a green economy.  As a result,
Rudenal has been listed among sustainable businesses eight times in a row
.
Through practical innovations, Rudenal has
helped millions of customers move towards a
better life.
Thanks to
that insurance policy, my child's life is the way it is
today.
The only thought I had was to buy insurance so that my
children and grandchildren would
n't be left behind.   He
still has his insurance money to cover his finances
.  He also hopes that
life will get better in the future.
Insurance is like a companion,
supporting you throughout your journey, from the
moment you fall and fully
recover, to the point where you receive your
payment. Both sides of the family have a
house now.
26 years of companionship, 26 years of continuous
innovation. Thank you for trusting Rudenal on our
journey to protect your loved ones
and build a sustainable future,
together realizing our mission of bringing
complete peace of mind to every Vietnamese family.